# **Stephanie Bippert**

404.630.3089 | stephaniebippert@hotmail.com 2111 Bishop Pointe, Marietta, GA 30062 stephaniebippert.com

Marketing and UX/UI Designer with over 3 years of relevant work experience, open to exploring part-time freelance and full-time opportunities. I'm a hardworking, detail-oriented person, but also have the ability to think "big picture", as demonstrated by starting the marketing department from the ground up in my current role at Kaizen Analytix. I am a leader, team player, and always open to trying something new and learning new skills.

#### **EDUCATION**

## University of Georgia

Bachelor of Business Administration in Marketing Area of Emphasis – Digital Marketing

**CERTIFICATIONS** 

UX Design, Career Foundry Google Analytics Google AdWords June 2021 September 2017 October 2017

GPA: 3.76 / 4.00

Athens, Georgia / May 2018

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Kaizen Analytix

Marketing Manager – Head of Marketing

Atlanta, GA (January 2020 – Current)

- · Creates, leads, and analyzes the success of the marketing and digital strategy and budget
- Responsible for lead generation, web design, SEO, SEM / PPC, content management, content creation, messaging and branding, visual design assets, etc.
- · Manages 2-person internal team, leads engagement with marketing agency, and works closely with C-Suite

## Marketing and Business Development Associate – Head of Marketing

Atlanta, GA (September 2018 – January 2020)

- Created, budgeted, executed, and analyzed the success of the marketing and digital strategy which included: website, SEO, PPC, content management and creation, social media, PR, business development, events, etc.
- Efforts resulted in a 10.1% decrease in bounce rate, a 37.8% increase in organic monthly website traffic, over 150% increase in followers across social platforms, and 52 qualified leads

#### **Ironmonger Brewing Company**

# Freelance, Digital Marketing Specialist

Marietta, GA (December 2019 – July 2020)

- · Designed all social media and advertising graphics
- Creates and manages success of Google Ads
- Advises overall marketing strategy and execution

# **Nottely Boat Club and Marina**

# Digital Marketing Intern

Blairsville, GA (January 2017 – August 2017)

- Managed company social media, lead content creation and photography efforts, and developed PR content for newspaper and radio ads
- Collaborated with Ironmonger Brewing Company to launch a soda brand called "Nott Soda" and a beer called "La Nott Beer". I also designed all associated product and advertising graphics.

### **SKILLS**

UX Design • UI Design • SEO • SEM / PPC • Design Systems • Prototyping • Mockups • Visual Design Marketing Strategy • User / Consumer Research • Digital Marketing • Social Media • Budgeting • HTML • CSS • Content Writing • Organization • Prioritization

## **TOOLS**

Figma • Google Analytics • Google Ads • InDesign • Adobe XD • Photoshop • Illustrator • Qualtrics • Survey Monkey • Mailchimp • Zapier • Jira • Bitbucket • WordPress • Elementor • Venngage • Microsoft Suite • LinkedIn • Facebook • Twitter • Instagram • Medium • PowerBi • Tableau